Chapter 2: Recuperation of the Royal Sisters

Rio picked up Flora, who had lost consciousness and fallen asleep. He carried Christina on his back and prepared to depart.

“Now, shall we get going? I won’t move that fast, but please hold on tightly to make sure you don’t fall off. You only have to cast the healing magic to a degree you can handle too,” Rio said to Christina before they left. Since he was carrying her on his back, her face was right before him when he turned to look over his shoulder.

“O-Okay...” Christina replied in a faint whisper.

What should I do? I stink, don’t I?

She was uneasy over that. She had sweat a ton walking around the forest, hadn’t had a bath, her dress was in tatters, and yet she had to cling to Rio in order to avoid being thrown off.

“She’s filthy and she reeks. I have no interest in holding such women.”

She recalled Duran’s words and felt even more uneasy; he had even said she looked just like a beggar. In contrast, there was a faint scent of soap on Rio, making her even more aware of her own body odor.

“Is something the matter?” Rio felt Christina stirring on his back and turned his head slightly to look at her.

“N-No, it’s nothing!” Christina shook her head, her voice sounding shrill. She casually slackened her hold around Rio.

“Umm, could you hold on a little more tightly?” he warned immediately.

“R-Right...” Christina hesitantly tightened her arms around Rio’s upper body. However, from how timid she was acting, it was clear she was still feeling reserved.

“Is there something wrong after all...?” Rio asked carefully.

Christina blushed and ducked her head. “I-It’s nothing, really...” she whispered. It was almost like the action of an ordinary shy girl—an unimaginable look for her usual dauntless self.

“That’s good, then... Oh, Your Highness wouldn’t normally have to cling to a man like this, right? I apologize for saying something so tactless. The journey won’t take long, but I’m sorry for this.” Rio seemed to realize the reason for Christina’s bashfulness and apologized awkwardly.

“Oh, no, that’s not it... I’m the one who should apologize for dirtying your clothing in such a state...” Christina explained in a faint voice. She wasn’t able to ask if she reeked, so she went about it indirectly.

Rio was finally convinced he didn’t need to worry with that. “If you’re going to say that, then my coat is stained with blood as well. I’ll have to prepare a change of clothes and a bath for us once we’re done traveling,” he chuckled.

“Thank you very much...” Christina quietly tightened her grip around Rio again.

“Now, let’s get going.” With Christina and Flora secured, Rio moved to leave. He kicked off from the ground and used wind spirit arts to float gently into the air. Then, once he reached an altitude of ten meters or so, Christina tightened her hold on him even more.

“Wha...” She glanced around, dropping her gaze down to the ground.

“You won’t fall, so don’t worry,” Rio said, guessing Christina’s thoughts from her reaction. He had revealed his flying spirit arts during his battle with Lucius, so he didn’t have to hide that anymore.

“Um... How are you flying right now?” Christina asked timidly.

“I’m manipulating the wind to fly,” Rio explained broadly. He had used his spirit arts without holding back in his fight with Lucius; it’d be impossible to explain every one of the abilities he used as an effect of his enchanted sword—Christina wouldn’t believe it. It was clear he’d have to explain spirit arts, but he hadn’t decided how much detail he’d have to go into yet.

“I-I see...” Christina hummed, looking around at the scenery in a daze. Perhaps she didn’t know how far she should pry, or perhaps her thoughts weren’t able to keep up with the series of shocking truths she’d been given. Perhaps it was both.

They were currently off the road at a hilly area with a great view, and she found herself captivated by the scenery.

“There’s a lot I have to explain, and I’m sure you have a lot of questions as well. It’s embarrassing to admit, but so much has happened that my head hasn’t caught up yet, so could you allow me some of your time for that once we’ve rested?”

“R-Right... That’s right, I have to treat your wound. Shall I start casting my magic around here?” Christina snapped back to her senses and extended the right arm she had reached around Rio’s chest. She placed her hand over his left arm where the bloodstain was and confirmed if treatment was required.

“Yes. But if you’re not in the right position to do so, it’s fine.”

“No, I can manage.” Christina uttered the spell Cura and a magic circle appeared by her right hand, glowing faintly. All that was left was to wait for time to pass. She watched Rio’s left arm closely.

“Thank you very much.”

“Uh... Y-You’re welcome.”

Because she had her arm extended out to heal, her face had moved right beside Rio’s before she realized it. When she noticed Rio’s face was close enough to kiss her if he turned his head, Christina immediately flushed bright red.

Despite that, she didn’t stop the treatment and continued casting her magic.

◇　◇　◇

Several minutes later, Rio arrived at a rocky area several kilometers southwest of where he fought Lucius.

This should do.

If the best place to hide a tree was a forest, then the best place for the stone house to blend into the surroundings would be a rocky area. The surroundings appeared to be uninhabited as well, so it was the perfect spot to set it up.

Showing them the stone house would end up revealing information he wanted to keep hidden, but with Flora in the state she was in, the situation was an emergency. Since bringing Christina and Flora to the city in their tattered dresses would just attract unwanted attention, he decided to set up a place where they could rest quickly.

“We’re landing here.” With that warning, Rio descended the dozen-odd meters to the ground.

“What are we doing in this rocky area...?” Christina looked around the area curiously. Rio landed soon after, allowing her to confirm that there really wasn’t anything of interest around.

“You can get down here.”

“Okay.” At Rio’s prompting, Christina obediently stepped down onto the ground. Meanwhile, Rio sent his magic essence through his feet and into the ground, using his spirit arts to flatten the foundation. His sword played a supplementary role to the activation of his spirit arts, so stabbing it into the ground would be faster, but his hands were full with Flora right now.

“The ground...is moving?” Christina muttered, looking down.

“I’m going to use an artifact with space sorcery to take out a house. This is just in preparation for that.”

“Huh...?”

“It may be faster to see for yourself. Dissolvo.” The foundation was flattened just at that moment, so Rio chanted the spell to use the Time-Space Cache he wore on his arm. Immediately after, the space before Rio and Christina distorted, and a huge boulder appeared with a heavy thud.

“Huh?” Christina blinked.

Rio ignored her and walked towards the entrance, opening the door nimbly while still carrying Flora. “Come in. This is the entrance. After you.” He knew there’d be no end if he started explaining everything, so he decided to put it off until he could explain everything at once later.

Christina was speechless for a long moment, but she eventually determined there’d be no end if she stopped to be surprised by everything.

“Okay...” she said, following Rio to the entrance. But the living space she entered was so comfortable, she lost her words once again. The stone house wasn’t decorated with the extravagant ornaments preferred by the noble class, but it was constructed far better than the average noble estate.

Rio entered the house after Christina and closed the door behind him. “I’d like to set Princess Flora down to sleep, but a change of clothes comes first, right? There are spare clothes that belong to Miharu and the other girls in the wardrobe room at the back. Can you go check to see if any are a suitable size?”

Rio had two stone houses: the one he first received, and the one he was gifted when leaving the spirit folk village with Sara and the others. Since it was a burden to carry clothes between the two houses, there was a spare set of clothes stored in each house for everyone.

They couldn’t go to the market to buy more clothes in their current state, so he decided to lend them those clothes and apologize to the girls later. Rio himself couldn’t pick out the clothes—especially the underwear—so he asked Christina to select them herself.

“...”

“Princess Christina?”

“Oh, r-right.” Still unable to shake off her state of shock, Christina looked around the room curiously. She only snapped back to her senses when Rio called her name.

“I’ll show you to the room where the spare clothes are stored, so could you please pick out a change of clothes for yourself and Princess Flora?” The change from the usually moody Christina to this person was new to Rio, who chuckled as he repeated his explanation.

“Right...” Christina nodded, embarrassed at how absorbed she had been in taking in the house.

“Once you find a suitable change of clothes, I’ll show you to the bathroom. If Princess Flora wakes up, you can give her a quick wash as well...”

“She looks a lot better now, so I’ll borrow some clothes and try to wake her.”

“Okay. For now, I’ll leave Princess Flora on the sofa and show you the way. Follow me.” Rio laid Flora down on the sofa and showed Christina to the wardrobe room. They arrived at the destination room a moment later.

“This is the wardrobe room. The closet has clothes that are hard to fold, and the drawers have the rest. The closet is shared, but the drawers are separated by person, so once you find something that fits you, you can stick to using that drawer. I’ll explain the situation to the girls who own the clothes later. Please come back to the living room where Princess Flora is once you’re done. I’ll excuse myself for now,” Rio explained, looking around the room. He normally never entered the room, so even he didn’t know whose clothes were located where.

“Thank you for doing all of this.”

“It’s not a problem at all.”

Christina bowed her head at Rio, who then left the room.

Now, to quickly borrow some clothes and return to Flora... She couldn’t keep Rio waiting for too long. Christina first opened a nearby drawer.

“This compartment is for underwear... It’s all made by the Ricca Guild too. This one has skirts, and this one has shirts. If we’re not traveling anymore today, something comfortable should be good, right?”

With that thought, Christina looked inside the closet. It was lined with tailored clothes like dresses and coats.

Wow... Just how many people lived in this house? she wondered, but it probably meant that she could find something her size. After that, Christina checked what kind of clothes were in the other drawers.

I’ll just pick a dress since it’s easy to put on.

She decided to borrow two dresses from the closet. The gowns she normally wore were too complicated to put on herself, but the dresses in the closet looked simple enough to wear easily. She held them up against her body to check their sizes, then picked one belonging to Sara and one belonging to Miharu. There was also a slip, so she borrowed that too.

This size should be all right... Probably.

She wouldn’t know how tight the clothes were until she actually wore them, but she’d dirty them with her dirt-stained body if she put them on like this. She was especially unsure about Flora’s size since she wasn’t here, but at worst she could borrow something else later.

I should head back.

Christina closed the closet door and drawers, leaving things the way they originally were before exiting the room.

Once she returned to the living room, she spotted Flora sleeping on the sofa. Where’s Sir Amakawa...?

“It looks like you found some clothes.”

Christina looked around the room to see Rio leaving the kitchen with a tray of drinks.

“Yes, I picked these dresses.”

“I’ve prepared some cold drinks, so please help yourself.” Rio placed the tray on the table. The ice clattered around inside the metal mugs, melting in the drinks.

“...” Christina gulped. She hadn’t been able to hydrate properly while walking around the forest, so her throat was parched.

“Go ahead—help yourself.” Rio immediately reached for his own cup.

“Thank you. I’ll drink it now.”

It must’ve been a hot tea cooled with ice. It hadn’t been cooled to an icy degree yet, so it was the perfect temperature to swallow down in one gulp.

Gulp, gulp. Christina drank the tea with vigor. Once her parched body was hydrated enough, she let out a dreamy sigh. “Phew...”

“There’s more if you’d like.” Rio immediately walked up to Christina and poured her a refill.

“I-I apologize. Drinking it all in one gulp must have been unsightly,” Christina realized with a start, cheeks flushing.

“It’s fine. Make sure you hydrate yourself properly.” Rio shook his head and smiled.

That made Christina’s face redden further. “Okay... Oh, umm. I have to wake Flora up as well. Flora, wake up.” She placed her cup on the table in a fluster and walked over to where Flora lay on the sofa. Then she gently shook her by the shoulder to wake her up.

“...” Flora must have been exhausted as she didn’t wake up. But Flora had been sweating a lot since being poisoned, so if she continued to sleep like this, she was in danger of becoming dehydrated.

“Flora. Flora?” Christina continued to call her name and shake her, forcing her to wake up.

“Mm...” Flora eventually opened her eyes, slowly.

“Thank goodness. Can you understand what I’m saying?”

“Christina...?”

“That’s right. You remember what happened, right?”

“Y-Yes... Sir Haruto came...then he gave me medicine...”

“After that, Sir Amakawa brought us to a safe location. You might still be feeling bad, but we can’t have you getting dehydrated, so you need to drink something. Can you sit up?”

“Yes...” Flora sat up with some support from Christina. Her gaze was still unfocused and bleary.

“Here you are.” Rio handed Flora’s cup to Christina.

“Go on, drink up.”

“Thank you very much...” Flora wet her parched throat with Christina supporting the cup for her. Her body must have been craving hydration, as she mindlessly continued drinking. After some time passed, she moved her mouth away from the cup with a cute gasp of air.

“I’ll pour you some more.” Rio approached Flora with the glass bottle of tea.

“Huh...? Sir Haruto?” Flora looked up blankly.

“Yes?” Rio cocked his head curiously.

“Ah... R-Right. You’re the one who saved me. My mind is still fuzzy...”

Apparently she hadn’t noticed Rio in her field of view until now. Now that she had rehydrated, her mind was clear enough for her to blush through the fatigue on her face.

“Your body must be exhausted. The poison’s been removed by the medicine, but you should still take it easy for a while.”

“How long will it take for her to fully recover?” Christina asked, worried for Flora.

“She’ll have a slight fever for a few days and she might feel sluggish, but once that’s gone, she’ll be fully healed. Is it okay if I send you two to Rodania after that?”

The spirit folks’ secret remedy was a powerful panacea that could heal everything other than bone fractures and external wounds, but it didn’t have an instant effect. Christina had also exhausted herself quite a bit, so the two of them would need to recover before they traveled.

“Will you take us there...?” Christina asked, watching Rio’s face.

“Of course.”

“But we’re...”

“Is there a reason why you shouldn’t return...?” Rio asked curiously.

“Sir Amakawa... You’re...the boy...” Christina faltered, looking guilty. Flora was watching Rio’s face with a similar expression.

“Are you referring to my past...?” Rio assumed.

Christina nodded heavily. “Y-Yes. We’re now aware of your identity.”

“And that’s the reason why I can’t take the two of you to Rodania, you’re saying?”

“The Beltrum Kingdom wasn’t good to you, and I don’t believe you have a favorable impression of me either. I’ve also treated you terribly.” Christina had a serious expression, brooding over the things they had once done to him.

“Speaking of terrible treatment... Come to think of it, the first time we met in the slums, you slapped me in the face,” Rio said, looking back on the past with a jesting laugh as though to clear the heavy atmosphere.

“Th-That’s... No, that too. I apologize sincerely for that. It was an extremely thoughtless action to take...” Christina recalled that moment as well and bowed her head with a blush.

“Y-You did something like that, Christina...?” Flora was taken aback and blinked blankly.

“Y-Yes. I saw you unconscious on Sir Amakawa’s back in the slums and flew into a rage...” Christina explained with a fading voice.

“If it’s about the slap, then I’m no longer bothered by it,” Rio said jokingly.

“That’s not all. When you were being harassed by the students at the Academy, I turned a blind eye to it all. And the biggest problem was during the outdoor drill...” Christina referred to that incident with a bitter look.

“Something did happen.”

The outdoor drill was the trigger that caused Rio to leave the Beltrum Kingdom. That had been the last time he had seen Christina and Flora under the name of Rio as well.

“At the time, I didn’t witness it myself, but I doubted the accusation that you were the one who pushed Flora off the cliff. Yet, despite that, I didn’t try to stand up for you,” Christina said shamefully.

“If you didn’t witness it, then you shouldn’t fabricate testimony.” Rio didn’t seem particularly bothered.

“Does this cat have its own will?” Christina asked, examining it closely.

“No, I’m just controlling it. Shall I move it to Princess Christina’s hand?”

Rio made the water cat jump down from Flora’s hand, walk across the table to Christina, then leap onto her hand instead.

“Wow, it really is cold to the touch. Even though it looks alive...” Christina blinked, looking down at the mini water cat. The cat then jumped back down to the table and trotted back to Rio, before vanishing without a trace.

“It was so cute...” Flora muttered in disappointment.

Christina cleared her throat to remind her sister of the time and place. “Flora...”

“R-Right.” Flora nodded.

“If you’d like, I can make it again after I’m done explaining things,” Rio chuckled. Flora’s eyes sparkled again at that.

Christina sighed, then recollected herself. “Spirit arts... It still uses magic essence like magic, right? As far as I know, it isn’t used in the Strahl region at all...”

“In regards to your first question, you are correct. As for its use, the technique became obsolete after the use of sorcery and magic was popularized during the Divine War.”

“Why did it become obsolete?”

“As I mentioned just now, spirit arts require a far longer amount of time to learn than magic. An amateur could learn to use magic in as fast as a month if they have the magic essence for it, right? As long as they succeed in taking the spell formula into their body, they can activate it even with imperfect control over their essence.”

“Right.”

“Meanwhile, in order to learn spirit arts to a usable level, the average person has to train for several years. Though this period can vary depending on talent.”

“It takes that long...” Christina’s eyes widened in wonder.

“Magic is a technique to alter the phenomena of the world, but you are aware most of the altering process is left to the spell formula, right?” said Rio. It was a topic learned in the Royal Academy.

“Yes,” Christina replied immediately.

“In spirit arts, the caster is the one who does the altering the spell would have done on the world. The training for that is what takes several years. The other reason it became obsolete would be because the commanders of the armies back then wanted to unify their troops by making them use the same magic, I suppose.”

“I see...”

“Also, you don’t have to pay too much attention to this part, but once you take a spell formula into your body, you become unable to use spirit arts. The reason why I was unable to use magic when I was in the Academy was because I could already use spirit arts back then.”

The real reason why Rio couldn’t learn magic was because he was contracted to a spirit at the time, but explaining Aishia and spirits was a bit too complicated, so he omitted it for now.

“So that’s why...” Christina and Flora were both wide-eyed.

“I explained spirit arts because it seemed necessary before I could talk about everything else, but I’ve digressed pretty far from the topic. Let’s go back to what happened after I fell from the cliff at the Royal Academy,” he said, getting back on topic. “After I fell from the cliff, I used spirit arts to land on the ground. I immediately climbed back up the cliff afterwards, but everyone was discussing who had pushed Princess Flora, so...”

Rio explained the truth that Christina and Flora weren’t aware of. Since he had told them about spirit arts already, he didn’t need to go into detail about how he survived the fall from the cliff.

“So you were there back then...” Christina grimaced, recalling the conversation that had taken place at the time.

“Yes. I was unable to show myself, so I watched the discussion from behind a tree. It was Duke Huguenot’s son himself who claimed that I shoved him, causing Princess Flora to fall off the cliff.” Rather than seeming mad, Rio had a tired smile on his face.

“I apologize for the situation...”

“I-I apologize too.”

Christina and Flora spoke with pale faces.

Rio shook his head flatly. “No. Princess Flora, you were a victim of the incident; and Princess Christina, you weren’t the one who falsely accused me. There’s no need for either of you to apologize.”

“But...”

“You didn’t see with your own eyes who pushed Princess Flora, right? And I recall Princess Flora tried to stand up for me. So please don’t worry about it,” Rio said, stopping Christina from objecting further.

“Do you know who pushed Flora off the cliff, Sir Amakawa?” Christina asked, seeking the truth.

“I do, but there’s no point in asking that now. There’s no guarantee that what I say will be the truth, and there’s no way of obtaining any objective evidence.”

“Even so, as I said yesterday, I believe in your words. Back then, Stewart Huguenot claimed that you lost your mind in fear of the ambush and shoved him when he was injured. But I cannot believe a warrior like you would lose yourself over an ambush of that scale,” Christina stated immediately. There wasn’t even a hint of doubt in her words.

“In that case, you can listen to this from the perspective of an eyewitness testimony. Do you remember how the monsters threw wooden spears from the forest and injured some of our squad? It was a very sudden ambush, so the scene immediately turned into chaos...”

As a result, everyone’s attention was turned to the attacking monsters, and no one witnessed the moment Flora was thrust off the cliff. This meant Rio was the only one who had seen things properly, so he added context to his explanation.

“Yes. Stewart was injured during that attack.”

“When he was injured by the spear, he started wailing for someone to pull it out and thrashed about in a panic.”

“Wait, does that mean he pushed Flora off the cliff?” Christina’s expression turned grim.

“It’s true that he was pushed first, causing Princess Flora to get caught in the process. The only difference in my testimony is that it wasn’t me who pushed Duke Huguenot’s son, but another male student he sought help from. And so, when Duke Huguenot’s son was pushed away, he crashed into Princess Flora and caused her to fall.”

“The male student who pushed Stewart must be aware he was the culprit, but was Stewart also aware that it was that male student who had pushed him?” Christina’s voice was trembling with anger.

“Most likely.”

He must have been looking at the face of the person he was seeking help from. “He knew, and he chose to blame you instead of that male student?”

“If he was truly aware, then that would be the case.”

“I truly cannot apologize enough,” Christina said, her face full of shame. She wasn’t just angry at the boys who tried to blame Rio, but also at herself for silently watching the whole thing take place.

“Not to repeat myself, but you do not need to feel any responsibility for the crime that I was accused of. I may have disappeared with a false accusation on my head, but I planned on leaving the Beltrum Kingdom after graduating from the Academy anyway. It merely hastened my departure,” Rio said casually, explaining how there was no need to be bothered by this.

“But if you weren’t falsely accused, you wouldn’t have had to use an alias like you do now,” Christina said, pointing out the inconvenience Rio was suffering right at this moment.

“That may be true, but if acting as a different person is all it takes to avoid involvement with the people who accused me of the crime, then I’m happy to do so.” Rio’s voice remained simple and steady as he spoke.

“Your view of this is too philosophical... You have more than enough reason to hate them, the Beltrum Kingdom, and the two of us. Yesterday, you said the things the Beltrum Kingdom and I did weren’t enough reason for you not to save us, but I cannot believe it. There’s no way you can feel so indifferent after suffering so much. Am I wrong?” Christina asked firmly, her refined face twisted in pain.

“I suppose it would be a lie to say I feel nothing... I have no intentions of retaliation, but big or small, I no longer trust Beltrum’s nobility.” Rio frowned, hesitating.

“It’s not something that can be settled with just distrust. It’s something worth hating for. You should be angry.”

So please act angrier at me, Christina implied bitterly.

“As someone who finally sated their desire for revenge against someone, I know how tiring it is to hate someone and feel constantly angry. Approaching someone I hate would be out of the question when I can just live my life forgetting them. So I’d rather leave myself distanced without any contact. I’ll save my anger for the things I cannot forgive and forget,” Rio said with a lopsided smile. Only he knew the weight of his words, as he had fulfilled his revenge.

“You’re... You’re truly too detached.”

Christina averted her eyes from Rio as though he was too bright to look at. She muttered with her head down, her voice nearly faded. Rio’s complete lack of malice had left her shocked and somewhat disappointed.

“That’s not true. A lot of the memories I have of Beltrum I can forget about with the passage of time, but there are some things that I absolutely cannot forgive.”

Rio purposefully increased the sharpness of his tone. He was recalling how Duke Huguenot had raised Latifa as a slave.

“What... What happened in our kingdom?”

“It involves someone other than myself, so...” So it wasn’t something he should tell them.

“Does it have to do with Professor Celia?” Christina asked.

“It doesn’t involve Celia, so please drop the subject. If I have a chance to tell you in the future, I shall do so then,” Rio said, slowly shaking his head.

“I understand...” Christina nodded, exchanging a look with Flora.

“We’ve somewhat strayed off track, but that’s basically why Your Highnesses shouldn’t feel any responsibility about what happened to me in Beltrum.”

“But...we still cannot allow that,” Christina protested with great difficulty.

“Why not?”

“Even if you hold no hate for me, I still did something terrible to you.”

“I did too! I caused Sir Haruto so much trouble...”

Christina and Flora both objected to Rio’s words.

“I don’t really know what you’re talking about... Princess Christina, are you possibly referring to the slapping incident?”

“L-Like I said, the slap was... No, the slap is part of it.” Christina blushed faintly, her spirit chipping away.

“I had a bad temper back then myself... It’s possible I glared at you rebelliously and scared you. I also touched a princess with my dirty hands,” Rio said jokingly.

“You weren’t dirty. You weren’t dirty at all!” Christina immediately interrupted firmly.

“Christina...?”

Flora looked at her sister in surprise—Christina didn’t raise her voice often.

“I was the dirty one—me. You had nothing but pure intentions, saving Flora as you did, yet I said horrible things to you in the slums. I was far dirtier than you.” Christina confessed her sins from her beautifully shaped lips.

“The situation was what it was.”

“There you go again...” Trying to forgive her. To Christina, that was brutally painful—but this could be her punishment. Rio forgave her, but she wouldn’t be able to forgive herself. And probably never would.

“Will you let me thank you and apologize? Even if you never make contact with me again as Rio, I want to express my remorse when interacting with you as Haruto.”

Now that she knew Haruto was Rio, an apology was absolutely necessary. On top of that, she would be indebted to Rio for the rest of her life. She wanted to repay that debt no matter what.

“I’ve already gotten words of gratitude and apology from you...” Rio made a pained face.

“Just saying it isn’t enough. This is a matter of sincerity. In addition to expressing my gratitude for every favor you have done for us, I apologize for all the wrongdoings that have occurred to you in the past. It’s not something that should be forgiven now, but allow me to swear that your kindness will never be returned with spite again.” Christina bowed her head towards Rio firmly.

“Thank you very much. And I’m very sorry. It was because of me that you became a wanted criminal. I’ve only ever caused you trouble...” Flora bowed her head like her sister.

“I understand. I forgive you, so there’s no need to go this far. What if I told you this: I had an ulterior motive in saving the two of you,” Rio said, a little flustered by the two princesses bowing at him.

“An ulterior motive?” Christina cocked her head.

“The stability of the Restoration means the guarantee of Celia’s safety and comfort. That’s why I want to send the two of you back to the organization. That is my intention behind protecting the two of you.”

So there’s really no need to feel overly indebted or worried about it, Rio more or less said without words.

“In that case, we’re sincerely grateful for Professor Celia’s kindness and your generosity,” Christina said with a hint of guilt in her smile, bowing her head once more.

Chapter 4: Meanwhile...

Just as Rio left the village with Christina and Flora, First Prince Duran of the Paladia Kingdom bid his farewell to Rio and stopped by the village before his return to the castle. The villagers watched him enter their village fearfully, but he didn’t even spare them a glance as he headed straight for the path that led to the main road. In his hand was Lucius’s sword that he’d gotten from Rio.

“Why, if it isn’t Prince Duran.”

Just as he was about to leave the village, someone appeared in Duran’s way. It was Reiss, the Proxia Empire’s ambassador.

“Oh? And when did you get here?” Duran replied with a grin.

“Moments ago. Just as Lucius was killed, in fact. Good grief, what a sly scheme,” Reiss lamented with a sigh as he protested.

Duran gave a dramatic shrug of his shoulders and feigned ignorance. “Hmm? I do not recall scheming anything.”

“You ignored my request in favor of Lucius’s, did you not?”

“I was merely told by Lucius that the plan had changed. There was no way for me to tell which request was the real one, so I believed the person who came to me directly.”

“Why did you give me a false location, then? It is a matter of fact that you deceived me regarding Haruto Amakawa and Lucius’s location. I ended up searching around an unrelated area because of you.”

After Lucius had used the teleport crystal to Paladia, Aishia pursued Reiss. Once he had barely made his getaway, he flew to Paladia and visited Duran. But when he asked about Rio and Lucius’s whereabouts, he was told Rio had been sent elsewhere and Lucius had gone after him.

“Bwa ha ha! That’s because the situation changed after I spoke to you. I don’t know how and why it changed, but Haruto reappeared before me once you left. Then Lucius reappeared as well. After that, I followed Lucius’s orders and lured Haruto to this village. But who would’ve expected Lucius to outwit a man like you? You sure seem panicked about it,” Duran lied smoothly, claiming his innocence with confidence.

“Indeed, I was utterly deceived this time...and went through quite the ordeal as a result. Well, what’s done is done. With Lucius dead, there’s no way of finding out the truth, and I don’t intend to punish you either.” Reiss sighed and backed away reluctantly.

“That aside, I’m impressed you made it here. How did you know this was the place?” Duran asked out of curiosity.

“There’s nothing to be impressed about considering I didn’t make it in time. I pretty much arrived just as the finishing blow was being dealt. As for how, well—it’s a secret,” Reiss said. He then looked at the sword in Duran’s hand.

Duran noticed Reiss’s gaze and tried to wrap up the conversation quickly. “Hmm. I suppose it doesn’t matter. So, what business do you have with me? I’d like to get back to the capital soon.”

“Now, don’t be hasty. I have a favor to ask of you—could you return that sword to me?”

“‘Return’? That’s strange. When Lucius was killed, Haruto became this sword’s owner, correct? And I received this from him because he said he didn’t need it. You’re telling me to return a sword that rightfully belongs to me?”

“That sword originally belonged to me—I let Lucius borrow it. I’m its true owner.”

“Do you have proof of that?” Duran chuckled with a grin.

“Of course, I won’t ask you to return it for free. I will offer several enchanted swords from our country in exchange.” It was an extraordinary offer.

“Oho, so you say this sword has the worth of several enchanted swords? I expected it to be exceptional based on the spell embedded within, but...” Duran didn’t bite right away.

“I won’t deny it, but that sword is a particularly evil blade with a past.”

“Are you saying it’s cursed?”

“I’m not certain, but that sword has a mind of its own. It savors the blood of the living and swallows the souls of those it kills. It’s said that it ultimately eats the soul of its owner too,” Reiss said with a creepy grin.

“A sword that eats its owner... You think I’ll be eaten?” Duran laughed heartily, then looked down at Lucius’s sword. The blade was completely enshrouded in darkness, reflecting no light at all.

“Well, that’s if you’re able to bring out the power of that sword in the first place. It’s rather particular about its owner. The sword won’t approve of you unless you’re a deviant like Lucius; someone who gives in to his negative emotions and enjoys killing others. If someone unsuited for the sword uses it, they’ll merely be swinging a sharp sword with a black blade.”

“Interesting. Let’s test that out,” Duran sneered, sending magic essence into Lucius’s sword. This was the way of testing aptitude for most enchanted swords in the world. If the wielder was found to be suitable for the blade, they would sense it right away.

“Hmph. No good, huh?” Duran huffed, unamused.

“Well? Do you feel like returning it now?” Reiss grinned.

“Fine, an exchange it is,” Duran agreed, clicking his tongue. “Bring the enchanted swords of your choice—I’ll hold on to this until then.” He was stubbornly thinking about having his knights test their aptitude for the sword.

“Understood. I shall return to the Proxia Empire on a later date and pick out several swords before sending a messenger to your castle. I have some minor business to attend to after this, so it won’t be immediate—but no longer than two or three weeks.” Reiss bowed his head with a fake-looking smile.

Duran narrowed his eyes. “Minor business, you say... Is it related to Haruto?”

“How sharp of you.” Reiss’s mouth warped with a chuckle, not bothering to hide anything.

“Isn’t it obvious? You asked me to cooperate in luring Haruto in the first place. Now that Lucius made the first move and failed, it’s only natural to assume your goal has yet to be achieved.”

In which case one would assume Reiss’s next target would be Haruto himself.

“I didn’t just fail at achieving my goal—it’s no longer possible to achieve at all now that Lucius is dead. My plan was to arrange a duel between Lucius and the boy, you see,” Reiss answered somberly.

“If so, I don’t see the reason why Lucius would act against you, since it seemed to me that he desired a duel with Haruto as well...” Why hadn’t the two cooperated with each other? Duran hadn’t heard anything regarding that from Lucius, so he cocked his head dubiously.

“I don’t understand either. Our goals and interests were perfectly aligned, yet for some reason Lucius couldn’t trust me as a partner. This is why humans are such...”

Mystifying creatures. Reiss sighed as though to say that.

“You certainly are the shadiest man I’ve ever met—enough to feel apprehension at the thought of entrusting my back to you in a war. I can relate to Lucius there,” Duran laughed heartily.

“I try to act as rationally as possible in order to be trusted, though.”

“Too rational. You should learn to be emotional when necessary.”

“Emotions, you say... Sounds difficult. Well then, I suppose I should leave now.” Reiss sneered, then made to leave the area. He was heading for the battlefield where Haruto had fought Lucius.

“Wait,” Duran called out.

“Yes?”

“I know you have your own mysteries, but you can’t win against Haruto.”

“I am aware. I nearly died when I fought him, after all.” Reiss nodded plainly at Duran’s blunt words.

“Why are you going after him? I watched his fight with Lucius, and it’s clear that you’ll be walking into your own death. I don’t care if you anger him and cause trouble for the Proxia Empire, but he’s also an honorary knight of Galarc, no? At worst, he could show up on the battlefield if Galarc and Proxia go to war. Paladia is allied with Proxia, so I’ll be at risk of facing him—and I don’t intend on fighting a lost battle, you know?” Duran emphasized with a sharp tone, putting some heat behind his words.

“I can follow that train of thought, but what do you want me to do about it?”

“I’m telling you to turn back if you’re going to provoke him needlessly. If Proxia’s ambassador shows up in a situation where the Beltrum princesses were abducted, then Proxia’s involvement in the incident will be assumed. The suspicion towards Paladia will also heighten.”

They were already toeing the edge of the gray zone in their current state, but if Reiss pulled something now, they’d be completely standing in the red zone.

Reiss gave a rare chuckle of amusement. “Ha ha ha! Harsh, but fair. Rest assured, I don’t plan on launching a surprise attack on him or anything. It wouldn’t have been an issue if Lucius had outwitted me and won, but the situation has changed now that he’s been defeated,” he replied seriously to Duran’s concerns about Rio.

“What do you intend on doing in the direction you’re heading, then?”

“They’re all important figures, you see—Princess Christina and Princess Flora included. I’m going to observe their next move from afar. But I won’t make a move on them while they’re still in the Paladia Kingdom. I do value my life somewhat,” Reiss said with a shrug, passing by Duran and walking away.

It’s none of my business if he drops dead somewhere... But he’s been acting more suspiciously ever since the heroes were summoned. Hmm.

Duran glared sharply at Reiss’s back and sensed that something unknown was about to occur.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, in the forest on the outskirts of Rodania, Celia was visiting the stone house with Aishia. The encounter with Reiss in Rodania, pursuing him with Aishia, and being retrieved by Orphia midway to hide in the stone house had all happened the day before yesterday.

Once Aishia defeated Reiss and returned to the stone house, Celia immediately left to check on the situation in Rodania. There she learned that Christina and Flora were missing and spent the entirety of yesterday in Rodania watching over the situation for any developments before sneaking out to the stone house today. Welcomed by Miharu, Latifa, Sara, Orphia, and Alma, she sat down on the sofa in the living room with Aishia.

“Thank you for the other day, everyone. I wanted to come visit yesterday, but a dire situation has cropped up in the Restoration.” Celia looked around at everyone as she thanked them, then sighed worriedly.

“What happened?” Sara asked.

“Princess Christina and Princess Flora have gone missing.”

“Huh...?” Everyone present was shocked.

“They apparently disappeared on their way back from the Galarc Kingdom. The enchanted ship they were on was attacked and many on board were killed,” Celia explained with a frown.

“They still haven’t been found yet, right? Do you have any leads...?” Orphia asked.

“They haven’t. There are no leads either. Their bodyguard, Vanessa, miraculously survived, but she lost so much blood that she’s still unconscious even now...”

“Vanessa...”

“Will she be all right...?”

Orphia and Alma worried.

“She’ll be fine... I think. Her wounds have been closed with healing magic, her breathing is stable, and she doesn’t have a fever or anything,” Celia explained.

“If there’s anything we can do to help out with the search for Christina...” Sara offered with a worried face. Sara, Orphia, and Alma had traveled together with Christina and Vanessa from Cleia to Rodania, so they weren’t strangers.

“Thank you,” Celia said happily, then immediately switched to a stern expression. “But you should stay and strengthen our defenses here. Aishia defeated Reiss, but the fact Princess Christina and Princess Flora were attacked is unsettling. You shouldn’t leave while Rio isn’t here.”

“I understand...” Sara nodded quietly.

“The timing is a little strange, though. Christina and Flora’s disappearance outside Rodania coincided with Reiss’s appearance inside Rodania... I imagine the two incidents are related,” Alma said thoughtfully.

“You think so too? We never found out Reiss’s goal in infiltrating the building either...” Even without evidence, the suspicion surrounding Reiss was there. Celia bit down on her lip listlessly.

Miharu hesitantly raised her hand. “Is it possible that you were his target?”

“Hmm... I don’t think so. He tried to flee as soon as we ran into him. And he actually fled too... I think it’d be more natural to assume he had business in the central office,” Celia answered. The fact Reiss’s first action had been to drop everything and run made her think she wasn’t the target.

“Did you tell the people of the Restoration that Reiss had snuck into the building?” Orphia asked.

“Yes. I informed them that a man resembling the Proxia Empire’s ambassador had snuck into the building and fled as soon as I saw him. No one else was there to witness it, so I hid Aishia’s presence, but...”

“What did the people of the Restoration say?” Alma asked.

“They pretty much had the same opinion as me—that he had snuck into the central office in order to steal something from the Restoration. They also said they’re considering the possibility of the airship attack being the work of the Proxia Empire or a collaborative effort between Reiss and Duke Arbor’s faction. Though they couldn’t see any reason why the ambassador himself would do something like this... They’ll be looking into it further alongside the search for the princesses.” When Celia finished speaking, she sighed heavily.

“Celia? You don’t look too good. Are you all right?” Latifa asked, staring at Celia’s face.

“Yeah, I’m fine.” Celia nodded with a gentle smile to reassure her, but it was still clear she was pushing herself.

Latifa turned her thoughts to Rio worriedly. “I hope Onii-chan comes home soon...”

A dozen or so griffin knights... While it isn’t more than I can handle, I may end up killing them. If the enemy is royalty, that might end up creating more trouble in the future... In which case...

It was time to retreat.

Rio stopped where he was and called out to the two princesses as he continued slashing away the rain of spells. “Princess Christina, Princess Flora. We’re withdrawing! Hold on to me when I give the signal. Understand?”

“Y-Yes!” the two behind him replied.

“Wh-What is with that man, honestly... We were so close to getting Estelle back too. If only I could kill him here...” Sylvie grimaced as she looked down at Rio on the ground. All the spells being cast had lethal force behind them, but they were being blown away with every swing of Rio’s sword. It was almost like there was an invisible wall of wind.

“Raaagh!” Renji roared, swinging his halberd at Rio from over ten meters away. A powerful blast of air cold enough to freeze the ground was released towards Rio.

“Sir Amakawa!” Christina yelled, sensing the danger. The cold air targeted Rio, whose attention was on the rain of spells from above. However, Rio released a violent burst of wind with a vertical slash, crushing the cold air Renji had sent. The air scattered across the courtyard and nearly blew away the soldiers on the walls.

“Wha?!”

“Guh...”

Renji and Arein were also in the courtyard and were almost swallowed up by the wind. It took everything in them to remain in place. The only ones who were unaffected were the griffin squad, but they were shaken by the disastrous sight of the courtyard.

“Wh-What are you doing?! Don’t ease up on your attacks! Fire!” Sylvie snapped back to her senses first and gave orders to those around her. The knights on the griffins chanted spells and made magic circles appear, but Rio pointed his sword upwards and created a dozen or so orbs of light. He fired them before the knights could finish casting their spells.

“What?!”

The trajectory of each orb was carefully controlled to directly strike every one of Sylvie’s griffin knights. He held back his strength in case there were any other important figures among them, but the orbs still had enough power to render the griffins incapable of flight. They descended to the ground unsteadily.

Rio used that chance to yell at Christina and Flora. “Now! Come to me!”

“Let’s go, Flora!”

“Right!”

The two hurried over to him and clung on to him tightly.

“Make sure you hold on tighter than usual!”

With that warning, Rio used the sword in his right hand as a catalyst to activate his spirit arts. A fierce wind wrapped around him and pushed his body upwards, accelerating his ascent into the air.

“Eek!”

Surprised by the unexpected speed of acceleration, Christina and Flora tightened their hold in a panic. They were going so fast, they instantly slipped past Sylvie’s side and out into the open air. Even the griffin Sylvie was riding lost its balance in midair in shock.

“Wh-What?!” Sylvie looked up at the skies in a panic.

Rio had ascended several meters above her already, accelerating as he began their flight through the air towards the southeast.

“Oh, is that so... There are lots of people anticipating our engagement, so I reckon it’d be better to meet their expectations...” Shaken by how directly he had been rejected, Hiroaki’s voice trembled.

“Who would those people be?” Liselotte asked calmly.

“Y’know, like the Galarc Kingdom and the Restoration. Christina and Flora disappearing has left things in a huge mess, after all. If we married for the sake of our respective parties, we’d be opening up the future for everyone.”

“In that case, you’d find a brighter future for the Restoration and Galarc in marrying Princess Rosalie instead of a duke’s daughter like me.” After all, it would be an engagement between a hero and a princess. They would naturally have a greater influence than a betrothal to a duke’s daughter as the third wife.

“I see... So the meeting is over, then.”

Hiroaki pursed his lips unhappily. The marriage discussion with Liselotte had ended in failure.

After that, Hiroaki and Liselotte returned to the drawing room with King Francois and Duke Huguenot to inform them of their decision. An awkward air hung in the room after they heard the result.

“Well, there was no point in getting engaged when we had no romantic interest in each other, I guess,” Hiroaki uttered indignantly, giving a short reason why the proposal had failed. The one who reacted with the most shock was Duke Huguenot—the engagement to Liselotte had been the condition Hiroaki required, so his composure faltered under his desire to speak to him right away.

Francois seemed to read the atmosphere. “There’s nothing that can be done if it wasn’t meant to be. Let us end this meeting here,” he announced.

“Sir Hiroaki, do you have a moment? You come along too, Roanna. We shall see you again later, Princess Rosalie.”

Duke Huguenot immediately left the room with Hiroaki and Roanna.

◇　◇　◇

“Rosalie, you may return to your quarters,” Francois said after the members of the Restoration had left the room.

“Yes, Father.”

Third Princess Rosalie left, leaving behind Francois, Liselotte, and her parents. The next moment, two figures stood at the doorway of the room. The Galarc king had summoned the hero, Sumeragi Satsuki, and Second Princess Charlotte.

“Can we enter now?”

“What a boring wait.”

Satsuki and Charlotte spoke up respectively.

Epilogue: Sakata’s Decision

With his marriage meeting with Liselotte ending in failure, Hiroaki left the drawing room and started marching away to vent the anger he held back in front of Liselotte. His walking pace was brisk.

“P-Please wait, Sir Hiroaki! Where are you going?” Roanna hurried after him.

“Back to my room. Leave me alone for a while. Save the talk for later.” Hiroaki kept his eyes forward. Duke Huguenot also followed after him at his brisk pace.

If he isn’t even allowing Roanna near him, he must be in a considerably bad mood. This isn’t the right time to discuss his marriage to Princess Rosalie. I do want to confirm his intentions on what to do about the engagement with her, but...it doesn’t seem possible right now, Duke Huguenot thought in a panic. Hiroaki was in such an irritated state, there was no telling what he could say.

Hiroaki had a vain sense of pride that made him pretend he wasn’t angry, but that facade was paper thin—it was very easy to see how intense his anger really was.

In reality, that was exactly what he was thinking.

Oh, I’m so over this. She just had to go and create an atmosphere to make me think I had a chance when she never planned on marrying me in the first place...

Hiroaki was building resentment towards Liselotte.

Ugh. Honestly, what do I do now? I used an engagement with Liselotte as a condition for marrying Rosalie, but...

Hiroaki and Rosalie’s engagement was still a highly confidential matter. Since it hadn’t been officially decided and announced, he could easily brush it off, but...

But if I reject Rosalie now, people will definitely think I’m not over Liselotte or something. Fuck this.

He had basically dug his own grave; his plan had completely turned on him. Hiroaki clicked his tongue and continued marching. He didn’t particularly dislike Rosalie—he just found thirteen-year-olds too childish. He did think there was future potential in her looks, so he didn’t have any complaints about actually marrying her. However, he was still unhappy with the situation, and his irritation was only growing.

Ugh, I wanna go back to Earth. I wanna go home and play games. Will I end up back on Earth if I jump from here and kill myself?

Hiroaki looked out the corridor window at the courtyard below and saw two familiar girls with lavender-colored hair.

“Huh...?” Hiroaki froze in his steps and stared at the two people walking through the courtyard. Or rather, three people. There was a gray-haired boy behind the two in front. It was Rio.

“So they’re alive...” Hiroaki muttered.

That was when Roanna and Duke Huguenot noticed the two in the courtyard as well.

“Princess Christina and Princess Flora?!” Roanna yelled in shock.

“Hah... Ha ha ha...” Even Duke Huguenot was in a rare daze state, the laughter spilling out of him not forced for once. With Christina and Flora alive, he no longer had to worry about the state of Hiroaki and Rosalie’s marriage; it filled him with a sense of relief.

“W-We have to go meet them! Duke Huguenot, Sir Hiroaki, let’s hurry!”

“Right.”

Roanna and Duke Huguenot hurried back down the corridor.

“Huh? Oh...” Hiroaki replied vaguely and watched the two of them disappear, then he looked back at the three people approaching the castle in the courtyard. Strangely enough, learning that the two princesses were alive didn’t fill him with any particular feelings of joy.

Good for them, I guess... But why are they with that bastard?

Inside Hiroaki’s chest, something burned quietly and intensely, yet coldly. Christina and Flora had happy expressions that he’d never seen on their faces, and they were walking at a distance much closer than when they had been with him. He didn’t like that.

“Hmm, so they’re alive... Which means Flora is reinstated as my first wife?”

He thought for another moment, then spoke up.

“I’ve decided... I’m going to get engaged to Rosalie,” Hiroaki murmured plainly but bitterly.